

299 Schaefer Street #2F Brooklyn, NY 11237 +1 (972) 979 0252 juno.a.mcclure@gmail.com

Juno A. McClure is a multidisciplinary artist and designer with major skill concentrations in interactive and game development, digital design, photography and education. Also, experienced in media research and emerging immersive media technologies.

TEACHING EXPERIENCE

2015- Assistant Professor of Game Design

Hostos Community College - City University of New York, Bronx, NY

2015 Part-time Lecturer (Creative Computation Lab)

Parsons School of Design, New York, NY

2014-2015 Teaching Assistant (Creative Coding - Processing and Arduino)

Parsons School of Design, New York, NY

2014 Code Teaching Fellow (Creative Coding - Processing)

Parsons School of Design, New York, NY

PROFESSIONAL AND RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

2009- Freelance / Independent Designer, Photographer, New York, NY

Clients Include: Art&Article, Demotix/Corbis Images, Seamless, HASH Magazine

2015 Front-End Web Developer

Try The World, New York, NY

2014-2015 Graduate Research Assistant

gadgITERATION, New York, NY

2014 Graduate Research Assistant

Parsons School of Design in collaboration with Maker Academy, New York, NY

2011-2012 Market Research Analyst

CoxReps, New York, NY

EDUCATION

2015 Master of Fine Arts, Design and Technology

Parsons School of Design, New York, NY

GPA 3.93 / University Merit, Dean's Merit Scholarships

2009 Bachelor of Arts, Communication - Media Production

University of Houston, Houston, TX

Minor in Studio Arts. Graduated with Honors, Cum Laude

PROFESSIONAL AFFILIATIONS

2016- Higher Education Video Game Alliance (HEVGA)2015- International Game Developers Association (IGDA)

2015- Interaction Design Association (IxDA)



 299
 Schaefer
 Street
 #2F

 Brooklyn,
 NY
 11237

 +1
 (972)
 979
 0252

 juno.a.mcclure@gmail.com

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Development C/C++, C#, OpenFrameworks, Java, Arduino, Raspberry Pi, OpenCV, GNU/Linux,

HTML 5, CSS3, Sass/SCSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, Git, CMS

Design Software Adobe CC (Photoshop, Lightroom, Illustrator, InDesign, Premiere, After Effects),

Unity, Maya, Blender, Audacity, Sketchup, GIMP, Inkscape

Addl. Skills Wireframing, Prototyping, Concept Design, UX Design, Photo Retouching, Physical

Computing, Photojournalism, Game Development, Market Research, Analytics

EXHIBITIONS AND HONORS

2018	The Earth Speaks, ARTSPACE Gallery, Stroudsburg, PA
2018	Unique Viewpoint, Fredericksburg Center for the Creative Arts Gallery, Fredericksburg, VA
2017	Halloween Game Expo, Playcrafting NYC/Microsoft, New York, NY
2017	Winter Play Game Expo, Playcrafting NYC/Microsoft, New York, NY
2017	People's Choice Salon Show, Greenpoint Gallery, Brooklyn, NY
2016	Halloween Game Expo, Playcrafting NYC/Microsoft, New York, NY
2015	Annual Summit Demo Day, NYC Media Lab, New York, NY
2015	Designing Multiplicity, Parsons School of Design, New York, NY
2015	2nd Annual Parsons Gala Art Exhibition/Auction, Parsons School of Design, New York, NY
2015	SXSW Student Work-The New School, SXSW, Austin, TX
2014	Annual Summit Demo Day, NYC Media Lab, New York, NY
2014	China-US Young Maker Competition Finalist, New York, NY / Beijing, China
2011	Dwell World Views Competition, Runner Up, Dwell Magazine

WORKSHOPS, PUBLIC SPEAKING AND REPUTATION

2018	"Educators Soapbox," Game Developers Conference, San Francisco, CA
2018	"Games for Engagement," "Mastering Tedium: Learning from Alternate Design Practices,"
	CUNY Games Conference 4.0, New York, NY
2017	"Twine in the Classroom," EdTech Innovation Celebration, Bronx, NY
2016	"Transforming Distance," Hostos Tertulia Series, Bronx, NY
2016	Parsons Design & Technology Job Forum 2016 (Panelist), New York, NY
2016	2016 CUNY Film Festival (Juror), New York, NY
2015	"Hack the Dinos" (Participant/Presenter), American Museum of Nat. History, New York, NY
2015	"VR101 with the Oculus Rift," Parsons Dorkshop, New York, NY
2014	"Photo Editing Workflow in Lightroom and Photoshop," Parsons Dorkshop, New York, NY
2014	"Digital Pathologies of the Metaverse," NUMA-Paris, Paris, France

PUBLISHED WORKS AND PUBLICITY

Print	After Dark (Book, 2016), The Elks Magazine (Magazine, June 2013), Security Management Magazine
	(June 2012), HASH (Quarterly Magazine, regular contributor), Subjective Ideal (Book, 2012), Dwell
	(Magazine, Sept. 2011), Dwell World Views (Book, 2011), Urban Dreamscapes (Book, 2010)

Web The Guardian, Kill Screen Magazine, Seamless, Consumerist, First Data Corp., Swamplot, Odyssey Networks, For The Love Of Brooklyn, Gothamist, Design Trust for Public Space, Houstonist